嘿 搞什么鬼
Hey, what the hell?
你差点要了我的命
You could've killed me!
你干什么呢
What are you doing?!
Campbell 你想向我解释
Campbell! You want to explain to me
为什么没接住那桶工具吗
why you didn't secure that equipment?
让它停下来 拜托
Make it stop. Please.
-让它停下来 -别怕 没事的
- Make it stop. - All-all right. All right.
冷静 士兵 怎么了
Calm down, sailor. What's wrong?
把它弄出去
Get it out.
-嘿 -把它从我的脑袋里弄出去
- Hey. - Get it out of my head!
嘿 来人给他些水
Hey, somebody get him some water.
水 谢谢
Water, please.
-嘿 没事的 -不 不
- Hey. It's okay. - No. No.
嘿 你会没事的 没事 嘿
Hey, you're gonna be all right. You're gonna be-- Hey!
NCIS 新奥尔良 S03E19
我跟你说 Pride
I'm telling you, Pride,
如果我想的是对的 那我就是错了
if I'm right about this, then I'm wrong.
不是说我自己错了
Well, not that-that I was wrong, per Se,
是之前的计算出了问题
but just that the initial calculations were incorrect.
但是因为那是FBI给的
But since those came from the FBI
-而不是我... -说人话
- and not me...- Rambling.
好吧 对不起
Right, sorry.
这是个正要面对的挑战
It's an ongoing challenge.
这几个星期里 我们来这儿很多次了
We've come out here many times in the last several weeks,
但目前还没有任何发现 能帮我们找出
and have yet to find anything to help us figure out
-杀害Javier Garcia的凶手 -好吧
- who killed Javier Garcia. - Okay, right.
那我们只能回到计算的问题
Well, that-that brings us back to the calculations.
我们的行动一直是基于
So, we've been operating under the belief
我们认为汽车炸弹雷管的向上推力
that the upward thrust of the car bomb's detonator
使弹片散落在一个同心圆弧里 对吧
sent the shrapnel out in a concentric arc, right?
是啊
Yeah?
但如果FBI没有考虑到
But what if the FBI never accounted
横向分散呢
for a-a lateral dispersion?
那爆炸区会更加不匀称
Well, then the blast zone would've been more asymmetrical?
完全正确
Exactly.
弹片会以完全不同的
Which would've sent the shrapnel out
轨迹散出去
in a whole different trajectory.
现在 如果我的推算是正确的
Now, if my calculations are right,
我们可能会找到些东西
we might be able to find something...
就在
...right around...
那儿
...there.
或者没有
Or not.
如果是 这样的东西呢
How about... something like this?
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
融化的金属
Melted metal,
向外隆起 对 没错
outward protuberance, yeah, yeah.
这可能是雷管上的
This-this could be from the detonator.
Pride 这可能就是我们一直在找的罪证
Pride, this might be the smoking gun we've been looking for.
但是烧得很焦了 应该在这儿很长时间了
Pretty charred though; been out here a long time.
你还能找到痕迹证据吗
Still think you can get trace evidence?
可以 相信我
Oh, yeah, believe me,
如果我能找到任何东西
if I can find anything
将Hamilton市长和Garcia的谋杀案联系起来 我会找到
to link Mayor Hamilton to Garcia's murder, I will.
我知道这对你的意义有多重大
I know how much this means to you.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们得暂时把这事搁在一边了
Well, we're gonna have to backburner it for now.
我们得工作了
We got to work.
在Belle Chasse有一名海军死了
Dead petty officer in Belle Chasse.
Belle Chasse海军基地
我们走吧
Let's go.
有什么发现 Christopher
What do we know, Christopher?
Robert Campbell军士
Petty Officer Robert Campbell,
Gulfport市的建筑支队的一员
a member of a construction detachment out of Gulfport,
从五层楼高的地方掉下来 原因不明
took a dive from five stories up for reasons unknown.
他自杀的吗
As in, he killed himself?
这就是我们来这儿要找的答案
That's what we're here to find out.
那是Campbell的主管
That was Campbell's officer in charge.
他说在Campbell跳下去之前
He said before Campbell jumped,
他说过他头很疼
he talked about a pain in his head,
疼得不能忍受
that he couldn't take it.
好的 有吸毒史或者
Okay. Any history of drug abuse,
心理问题吗
psychological issues?
心理评估正常 药检没问题
Well, psych eval's normal, drug tests clean.
我没有发现任何异常的指标
Nothing I can see here that would raise any red flags.
我询问了他团队里的几乎每一个人
I questioned nearly every man in his unit;
他们都说Campbell充满活力
they all said Campbell was full of life,
完全想不到他会这么做
the last guy they'd expect that from.
一个人不会无缘无故跳楼
A man doesn't just jump for no reason.
有些东西把他逼到了边缘
Something drove him over the edge.
得弄清楚 Loretta
Need to know what. Loretta.
从严重的头部外伤
Well, judging from the massive head trauma
以及耳朵 鼻子 嘴巴里溢出的血来推断
and the hemorrhaging from the ears, nose and mouth...
毫无疑问 Campbell死于
...there's no doubt Campbell died
坠落的冲力
from the impact of the fall.
他在跳楼之前 曾抱怨说头疼
He complained of head pain just before he jumped.
有迹象表明头疼的原因吗
Any indication of what caused it?
我需要解剖尸体才知道
I'd have to get him into autopsy,
但有件事很奇怪
but there was one thing peculiar.
他的眼睛有黄疸
His eyes are jaundiced.
并不是坠落造成的
That didn't happen from the fall.
但有可能是先前就有的疾病造成的
But some pre-existing condition could've made that happen.
胆结石 胆汁梗阻
Yeah, gallstones, bile obstructions.
我想便秘是不会
Something tells me constipation
把他推下平台的
isn't what pushed him over the ledge.
Pride探员
Agent Pride?
我是Lopez少校
Lieutenant Commander Lopez.
很抱歉我没在这里迎接你
I'm sorry I wasn't here to greet you.
我得跟基地的指挥官报告情况
I had to update the base C.O.
少校
Commander.
Campbell军士是你的手下吗
P.O. Campbell's one of yours?
我一直在这儿监督海军工兵的工作
I've been overseeing the Seabees' work here,
军队里最优秀的40名士兵
40 of the finest men in uniform.
对于你的损失我很抱歉
I'm sorry for your loss.
知道为什么Campbell会这样吗
Any idea why Campbell might've done this?
不 不知道
No, none.
他一直很准时 一直在工作 非常努力
He's been on time and on task, and working his tail off
与其他人一起完成安装工作
with the rest of my men to complete the install.
你们正在安装的是什么
What is it that you're installing here?
高速光纤电缆
High-speed fiber optic cable.
给整栋建筑物架线
Wiring the entire building.
把这些人从Gulfport市送到这里 只是为了架线吗
Travel these men down from Gulfport just to lay some cable?
基地最新的信息技术大楼
The base's newest I.T. building.
出于各种原因
Getting it online
上网都是最重要的
is paramount for a variety of reasons.
你介意我去看看其余的人吗
Do you mind if I go check up on the rest of my men?
他们被吓得不轻
They're pretty shaken.
没问题
Course.
有什么不对劲吗
Something wrong?
没有 只是
No, just...
带一个分队过来
seems strange to bring down a detachment unit
只为了安装光缆 这挺奇怪的
just to install fiber optic cable.
这是一次非常专业的安装
Well, it is a pretty specialized install.
嘿 来看看这个
Hey, check this out.
我刚大概看了一下Campbell团队的情况
I just did a quick rundown on Campbell's unit.
看起来他不是唯一一个
Looks like he wasn't the only one
不舒服的
not feeling well.
Bryan Howard军士
All right, Petty Officer Bryan Howard
昨晚登记入住了
apparently checked himself into
基地的诊所
the base clinic last night,
他现在生病待在营房里
and he is now sick in quarters.
感觉那个少校应该要提到这点
You'd think the commander would've mentioned that.
Sebstian 等Wade准备好了
Sebastian, go with Wade back to the morgue,
就跟她一起回停尸房
when she's ready.
你们一旦查明
Let me know as soon as you find out
折磨Campbell的病因 就马上告诉我
what Campbell might've been suffering from.
在这期间 我们去见见Howard军士
Meanwhile, we'll go pay Petty Officer Howard a visit.
我半夜醒来
I woke up in the middle of the night,
脑袋发胀 就好像要爆炸一样
felt this pressure, like my head was gonna burst.
按道理不应该这样
Thoughts weren't making any sense.
当时真的生不如死
It was scary as hell, man.
所以你去门诊部做了检查吗
So you checked yourself into the clinic?
医生说我有脱水症
Doc said I had dehydration sickness.
给我输了液 开了镇静剂 就让我回去了
Gave me some fluids, sedatives, sent me on my way.
整整一周 你都和Campbell一起在那个脚手架上
Well, you were up on that scaffolding with Campbell
在阳光下暴晒 干你们的那些活 是吗
all week, exposed to the sun, working your butt off, right?
是的
That's right.
所以 脱水症 中暑
So, dehydration, heat stroke--
或许这才是原因所在
maybe that's what this is.
如果真是那样 他应该会有所好转 而不会更糟
If that's all this is, he should be getting better, not worse.
能否让我看一下
You mind?
他的眼睛有黄疸症 跟Campbell的一样
His eyes are jaundiced, just like Campbell's.
哇 你是说
Whoa, whoa, whoa, are you saying
我现在得了让Robert跳楼的病吗
whatever I've got's what made Robert jump?
不 我们并没有下任何结论 士兵
No, we're not saying anything, sailor.
我们只是想弄清楚发生了什么
We're just trying to figure out what happened.
所以 你半夜醒过来
So, you woke up in the middle of the night,
很难受
sick.
知道原因吗
Any idea what caused it?
我不知道
I don't know.
Campbell什么时候开始有这些症状的
When did Campbell start showing symptoms?
-大概是相同的时间吗 -是 差不多
- Around the same time? - Yeah, about.
但他只是上床休息
But he just went back to bed.
Campbell强壮得很 你知道吗
Look, Campbell was a beast, okay?
就算他挨了枪子 他也能回去继续工作
He probably could've taken a bullet and gone back to work.
还有其他人生病吗
Anybody else get sick?
我是说 这里肯定有什么问题
I mean, something's going around.
你跟别人分过食物或喝的吗
You share any food or drink?
没有 不过
No. Although...
不过什么
Although what?
我们收到过一个国王蛋糕
We had a king cake delivered to us.
我们都吃了一些
We all had some.
谁寄给你们的
Delivered by who?
纸条上只是写着 "欢迎来到Belle Chasse基地"
The note just said, “Welcome to Belle Chasse.”
我们并没有吃完蛋糕
We didn't eat all of it.
我觉得Robert把剩下的藏在他的箱子里了
I think Robert stashed the rest in his foot locker.
Angelo Brocato的蛋糕
Angelo Brocato's cakes.
成立于1905的新奥尔良品牌，被视为当地慈善机构，经历Katrina飓风后，被洪水冲毁
哇
Whoa.
King
King,
看看这个
take a look at this.
眼睛出血 口吐白沫
Blood in the eyes, foam in the mouth.
不可能只是食物中毒这么简单吧
No way that's just from food poisoning, right?
不可能
No way.
知道我们遇到的是什么毒吗
Any idea what kind of poison we might be dealing with here?
我把常见的毒物都测试了一遍
I've tested all the usual suspects--
氰化物 砷 士的宁 结果都是阴性
cyanide, arsenic, strychnine-- they all came back negative.
是 我还测试了蓖麻毒素 沙林 还有毒箭蛙
Yeah, and I checked for ricin, sarin and poison arrow frog.
也不匹配
No match.
但可以肯定的是 某种毒药
Still, some type of poison
使Campbell士官的细胞发生异变
mutated Petty Officer Campbell's cells,
造成了严重的脑肿胀
caused severe brain swelling.
这就解释了是什么逼他跳下去的
That explains what drove him off the ledge.
你知道 河豚毒素可以造成细胞突变
You know, tetrodotoxin could've caused cell mutation,
但是它 它比杀害Campbell的毒药反应要快
but it... it's faster acting than what killed Campbell.
你有检查钋吗
Have you checked for polonium?
嘿
Hey.
为什么你们没有一起工作
Why aren't the two of you working side by side?
Sebastian有点疑病症
Sebastian's a bit of a hypochondriac.
或者说 有些人只是更谨慎一些
Or, you know, some people might just say extra careful.
你知道的 我对毒药有点害怕
You know. I-I have a thing about poisons.
就像有些人怕蛇
It's like how some people are
怕蜘蛛 怕马戏团的小丑
afraid of snakes or spiders or.. circus clowns, you know.
Campbell所在队伍的另外四名工兵
Four more Seabees from Campbell's unit were just
刚刚去看了门诊
admitted into a clinic,
而且Howard士官的病情更严重了
and Petty Officer Howard is getting sicker.
基地指挥官将他们都隔离了
The base C.O. is isolating them
直到查明病因
until they know what's causing it.
很奇怪的是 这个毒药对每个人的影响
It's odd that it's affecting people
都非常不一样
at vastly different rates.
毒药一般并不是这样的
Poisons don't usually work that way.
所以我们需要在病人死亡之前
Then we need to find out what does
找到答案
before we lose anyone else.
Sebastian 和Loretta一起
Sebastian, work with Loretta,
并肩作战 寻找线索
side by side, and learn things.
好吧 但是...
Okay, but the...
我们需要知道是谁订了那个蛋糕 Patton
Need to know who ordered that cake, Patton.
我希望我能告诉你 但是
And I wish I can tell you, but I can't
我从蛋糕店的电话记录中查不到任何人
get anybody from the bakery on the phone.
这个时间 很奇怪
This time of day, that's strange.
是的 但是我跟基地核查过了 根据
Yeah, but I did check with the base, and according to
他们的进门记录 Angelo Brocato确实在晚上九点的时候
their gate log, Angelo Brocato did, in fact, deliver a cake
-送了一份蛋糕 -地址上是寄给谁
- at 21:00 hours. - Addressed to who?
没有具体的名字 只写了53号兵营
No name in particular, just Barracks 53.
Campbell的部门 看来他们就是目标
Campbell's unit. Sounds like they were targeted.
为什么 一群在架线的工兵
Why? Bunch of Seabees installing cables.
可能不是
Yeah, maybe not.
Christopher Gregorio 你们去Angelo Brocato's
Christopher, Gregorio, go to Angelo Brocato's.
我要知道是谁订了那个蛋糕
I want to know who sent that cake.
Patton 检索在蛋糕店附近的
Patton, search surveillance cameras
摄像头录像
around the bakery,
把昨天进出过蛋糕店的所有人的身份都查出来
I.D. everyone who came in and out of there yesterday.
-明白 -你在给谁打电话
- Copy that. - Who you calling?
Belle Chasse基地 请找Lopez少校
Belle Chasse. Commander Lopez, please.
我想知道这些工兵到底在做什么
I want to know what those Seabees were really doing.
告诉她 我是NCIS探员Pride
Tell her it's Agent Pride, NCIS.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
联邦探员 你在这儿上班吗
Federal agents. You work here?
嗯 是的
Um, yeah.
怎么了 有什么事吗
Why? Is there something wrong?
蛋糕店通常在这个点还关着门吗
The bakery usually closed at this hour?
不是
No.
应该是几个小时前就开的
Should've been open hours ago.
我刚到这儿 准备上下午的班
I mean, I just got here for my afternoon shift.
我不知道为什么我的老板没有给我打电话
I don't know why my boss didn't call me.
老实说 我有点担心
Honestly, I'm a little worried.
门是开着的
Door's open.
哦 不 黄疸症的眼睛和口吐白沫
Oh, no. Jaundiced eyes and foaming at the mouth.
和工兵们一样的症状
Same symptoms as the Seabees.
是吃了同一个蛋糕吗
From sampling the same cake?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
他的胳膊和手上有防御伤
He's got defensive wounds on his arms and hands.
看来他跟人搏斗过
Looks like he put up a fight.
最后输了
And lost.
这个世界到底怎么了
What in the world is going on here?
从我记事儿以来 Richard Logan就一直
Richard Logan's been working at Angelo Brocato's
在Angelo Brocato's工作
for as long as I can remember.
没错 也是他们最好的糕点师
Yeah, best pastry chef they've got, too.
人们会点名要订他的国王蛋糕
Folks order his king cakes by name.
他给工兵的蛋糕下毒只可能是...
Only way he would've poisoned the Seabees' cake...
他是被人强迫这样做的
Is if he was forced into doing it.
医生说凶手敲晕了Logan
Doc says the killer knocked out Logan
并且一定给他注射了
and must have injected him
与杀害工兵的相同毒药
with the same poison that killed our Seabee.
她得出死亡时间了吗
She got time of death?
是 昨晚九点到十点之间
Yes. Between 9:00 and 10:00 last night,
根据Patton的发现 与蛋糕被送到基地
which, according to Patton, is the same time
是在同一时间
the cake was delivered to the base.
所以凶手等到顾客都离开了
So killer waits for customers to leave,
强迫蛋糕师给蛋糕下毒
forces the baker to poison the cake,
然后就等着 直到蛋糕被送到再杀了他 为什么
and then waits... until it's delivered to kill him? Why?
凶手可能不希望
Killer probably didn't want
Logan认出他 想要掩饰他的行踪
Logan to I.D. him-- tried to cover his tracks.
是 但却把Logan的尸体留给我们去研究
Yeah, but by leaving Logan's body for us to find,
什么都有可能 除了
it does anything but.
粗心
Sloppy.
-这说不通啊 -是的
- It doesn't make sense. - Yeah.
不过 你觉得这些工兵是目标吗
Still, you think our Seabees were targeted?
没有理由不是
No reason not to.
尤其是 我联系不到Lopez少校
Especially since I can't get in contact with Commander Lopez.
甚至问过她在Gulfport市的
Even checked with her C.O.
-指挥官 -你觉得她失踪了吗
- at Gulfport. - Think she went U.A.?
在Belle Chasse基地的指挥官
The base C.O. at Belle Chasse checked
检查了外出记录 说她在我们今早离开后
the exit logs; says that she left
就立马离开了
right after we did this morning.
等等 我们现在是把她当嫌疑人了吗
So, wait, are we thinking she's a suspect now?
只有找到她才能知道
Well, only way to know is to find her.
哈 领先你们一步
Ah. One step ahead of y'all.
看看这个
Check it out.
我刚才在排查蛋糕店周围的
I was combing through surveillance footage
监控录像
around the bakery.
没有发现可疑的顾客
Not a suspicious customer in sight,
直到 我决定扩大搜索范围
until... I decided to expand my search window.
看
Voila.
Lopez少校
Commander Lopez.
Lopez 她去那儿做什么
Lopez? What is she doing there?
这是什么时候的录像
When was this taken?
大概一个半小时前
About a hour and a half ago.
就在Tammy和我到那儿之前
That's right before Tammy and I got there.
会不会是我们把她赶走了
Think we chased her away?
但还是不知道 她一开始去那儿做什么
Well, still, what was she doing there in the first place?
尤其是 面包师已经死了好几个小时
Especially considering the baker had been dead for hours.
太多事情串不起来 而现在没人跟我们解释
Yeah, too many things don't add up, and no one's talking to us.
我一会给Vance主任打电话
I'll call Director Vance.
看他能不能跳过这些官僚程序
See if he can cut through this bureaucracy.
伙计们 我们有大麻烦了
Guys, we got big problems.
对 恐怕非常不乐观 Dwayne
Yeah, I'm afraid it's not good, Dwayne.
不 这比不乐观糟糕多了
No, it's worse than not good.
实验结果证明 蛋糕不是被下毒了
It turns out that the cake wasn't spiked with a poison,
而是被注入一种病毒
it was injected with a virus.
当我无法识别是什么毒时 我重新检测了一遍
When I couldn't identify the poison, I rechecked
被感染的细胞分子结构
the molecular structure of the affected cells...
然后发现它其实是
And discovered that it was actually infested
被极小的
with microscopic,
单链RNA感染了
single-strand RNAs.
也就是病毒
Which means virus?
对 但不是一般的病毒
Yeah, but not just any virus.
而是一种超级病毒 就像是
A supervirus-- we're talking
刚果出血热 登革热 埃博拉病毒
Congolese hemorrhagic fever, dengue, Ebola
加在一起那么厉害
all rolled into one.
他是传染性的吗
Is it contagious?
传染性极强 但幸运的是 不是空气传播
Very. But fortunately not airborne.
是的 唯一感染途径是
Right. The only way to contract it is
吸收 就像吃国王蛋糕这样
either through ingestion, like with the king cake,
或者接触 与感染者的任何皮肤接触
or by touch, so any skin-to-skin contact
都有传染风险
with the infected can risk exposure.
这也就包括了 任何接触过工兵
Means anyone who's been around our Seabees
或者蛋糕的人
or the cake could get it.
整个基地都有危险
The whole base could be in danger.
我们也是
So could we.
虽然我们之中还没人出现症状
Except none of us have shown any symptoms yet.
但我们也不能冒险
Still no reason to take chances.
我们得待在办公室 直到我们都做完检测
We stay put in the office till we all get tested.
有治愈的办法吗
Is there a cure?
据我所知 还没有
Not that I know of.
King
King.
这可能不只是针对工兵的袭击
This could be more than just an attack on our Seabees.
这可能是生物恐怖袭击
Could be bioterrorism.
给基地指挥官打电话
Get the base C.O. on the phone.
我们需要封锁Belle Chasse基地
We're gonna lock down Belle Chasse.
我们不能让病毒传播
We cannot let this get out.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
恐怕已经传播出来了
I'm afraid it already has.
Wade医生
Dr. Wade?
哦 拜托 我们在浪费宝贵的时间
Oh, please, we're wasting valuable time.
-就让我工作吧 -好的 女士
- Let me just work. - Yes, ma'am.
Loretta
Loretta!
Loretta.
告诉我 Loretta 怎么回事
Talk to me, Loretta. How did this happen?
我一定是在
It must have happened
犯罪现场感染的
at the crime scene.
没穿消毒服 我的皮肤外露
Without my scrub suit on, my skin was exposed.
然后你接触Campbell的尸体了
And you handled Campbell's body?
对 血液微粒 唾液 汗液
Yeah. Blood particulates, saliva, sweat.
不需要很多就会感染
Doesn't take much.
我想你和你的小队应该没事
I assume you and your team are all right.
对 我们的检测结果都是阴性的
Yeah, we-we all tested negative.
谢天谢地
Ah, thank God for that.
Sebastian也没事
Sebastian cleared, too.
下次 记得提醒我不要嘲笑
Next time, remind me not to tease him
他老是疑神疑鬼的 那没准能救命
about being a hypochondriac-- it may have saved his life.
你不应该休息吗 Loretta
Should you rest, Loretta?
没有时间休息了
There's no time to rest,
尤其是现在还有其他感染者
not with others being infected, too,
如果我们不能阻止病毒扩散
and more to come
还将有更多的感染者
if we can't stop this virus from spreading.
Belle Chasse基地的情况怎么样
The situation at Belle Chasse?
基地已经封锁 感染的人已经隔离
Base is locked down, the sick quarantined.
海洋化学和生物事件响应部队
Marine Chemical and Biological Incident Response Force
已经在路上了
is on its way.
目前为止有多少感染者
How many infected so far?
一共七个 四个是Campbell的工兵同事
Seven total-- four of Campbell's Seabees,
三个是和他们同一营房的机械师
three machinists who shared the barracks with them.
烧掉他们的衣服和所有物品
Burn their clothing, all their belongings.
虽然不通过空气传播
It's not airborne,
但显然有极高的传染性
but obviously it's highly contagious.
并且致命 如果我们找不到治愈的办法
Deadly, if we can't find the cure.
我们还有多长时间
How much time do we have?
你是说我还剩多长时间吗
You mean how much time do I have?
这个么
Well...
病毒对每个人的影响不一样
the virus affects everybody differently.
但我在工作的同时一直在监测我体内的病毒
But I am monitoring my viral load while I work,
看它使我全部白细胞变异要多久
see how quickly it mutates my white blood cells.
我估计大概
I would say maybe...
10个 11个小时就会...
ten, 11 hours before...
我不敢相信这会发生
I can't believe that this is happening.
她现在怎么样了
How's she doing?
害怕 就和我们一样
Scared, like the rest of us.
她就靠我们了 Sebastian
She's counting on us, Sebastian.
集中注意力 为了所有人
Stay focused, for everybody's sake.
说起来容易 做起来难
Yeah, easier said than done.
病毒库有匹配结果了
Got a match from the viral database.
-QR6 -那是什么
- QR6. - What is that?
那是由中国军队研究出来的超级病毒
It's a-a supervirus developed by the Chinese military,
但正常来讲 不可能从他们的实验室泄露出来
but supposedly, it never left their lab.
Pride 如果是这个 那这就是一次生物恐怖袭击
Pride, if this is right, then this has to be bioterrorism.
这是毫无疑问的
I mean, there's no two ways about it.
但为什么是现在 为什么选Belle Chasse基地
But why now? Why Belle Chasse?
我不知道
I don't know.
唯一的好消息是他们不可能
I mean, the only good news is that there's no way
研究出这么致命的病毒
they would have developed this lethal a bug
而不研究解毒剂
without also developing an antidote.
所以就算Loretta研究不出解药
So even if Loretta can't come up with a cure...
对 我们可以 只要我们能找到
Yeah, then we can, as long as we can
给国王蛋糕下毒的人
find whoever infected that king cake.
因为他们没有被感染
'Cause they'll probably have the antidote,
所以他们很有可能有解药
since they don't want to get infected, too.
唯一的问题就是 我们没有那么多时间
Only problem is we don't have that much time.
好吧 你待在这 帮Loretta
All right, stay here, help Loretta.
等等 你等一下 你得带我去基地
Wait, hold on, you got to get me on that base.
什么
What?
受害者被感染的程度不一样 对吧
Victims are being infected at different rates, right?
也就是说 有一些人比其他人对病毒更有抵抗力
Which means some are more resistant to the virus than others.
如果我能检测他们的血液 也许我能研究出解药
If I can test their blood, then maybe I can create my own cure.
我 我不能让你也冒着被感染的风险
I'm-I'm not willing to risk you getting sick, too...
这不是你的选择
That's not your choice!
求你了 Pride
Please, Pride.
我 我知道你想要
I-I know that you want
尽你所能去救Loretta
to do everything you can to save Loretta,
但我也是 好吗
but so do I, all right?
我不能 失去她
I-I can't lose her.
我们不会失去她的 Sebastian
We're not gonna lose her, Sebastian.
我会安排你和海洋生物响应部队一起
I'll get you on with the Marine Bio Response Force.
你和他们合作 但听我说
You work with them, but listen to me--
生化防护衣
Hazmat suit,
手腕带 所有的防护
wrist tape, the works.
我一样不能失去你
I can't lose you, either.
哦 等等 Pride
Oh, wait. Pride.
Pride
Pride.
我差点忘了 呃
I almost forgot. Uh...
我从那个 Garcia的弹片上
I was able to get a partial fingerprint
得到了一个局部的指纹
off of that, uh, Garcia shrapnel.
不足以确认身份
It's not enough for an I.D.,
而且显然不可能将炸弹
and obviously it's no way to tie the bombing
和Hamilton市长联系起来 但这是个开始
to Mayor Hamilton, but it's a start.
好 你为什么现在告诉我
Okay, wh-why are you showing me this now?
就是 万一我出了什么事
Just, you know, in case something happens to me.
我们以后再研究这个 Sebastian 我们一起
We'll work on this later, Sebastian, together.
集中注意力
Focus.
Pride探员
Agent Pride.
刚和海军情报办公室通过电话
Just got off the phone with the Office of Naval Intelligence.
他们终于承认Lopez少校和她的团队
Finally admitted that Commander Lopez and her team
在Belle Chasse安装的
were doing more than just
并不只是电缆
installing cable at Belle Chasse.
-还有别的 那是什么 -还不知道
- More, meaning what? - Don't know yet.
海军情报办需要许可才能告诉我们详情
ONI needs clearance to get us read in.
很明显 这是被归类为高级机密的
Apparently, it's top secret, compartmentalized.
他们想继续保密
They want to keep it that way
直到他们掌握了更多内容
until they can get more specifics
关于中国人到底想要的是什么
about what the Chinese are really after.
瞄准了参与机密建设的工兵营
Targeting Seabees on a top secret project
这对他们来说还不够吗
not specific enough for them?
他们觉得 知道项目具体内容的人
The less people know exactly what the project is,
越少越好
the better, far as they're concerned.
海军情报办想要我们专心去抓该为此事负责的人
ONI just wants us focusing on catching whoever's responsible.
Lopez少校呢 他们找到她了吗
What about Commander Lopez? Did they hear from her?
没 所以他们有些担心
No. And they're worried.
事实上 是他们派她到蛋糕店
Turns out they're the ones who sent her to the bakery
暗中调查
to quietly investigate.
也许她从她手下那儿听说了国王蛋糕的事
Well, maybe she heard about the king cake from her men.
至少解释了她为什么在那儿
At least that explains why she was there.
没错 但不能解释她为什么消失了
Yeah, but not why she disappeared.
监视名单上有什么发现
You find anything on the watch list?
这是一个跟国家安全部有关的中国人名单
Yeah, a list of Chinese nationals linked to MSS,
但是得花我们一周才能缩小范围
but it'll take us all week to narrow it down.
Loretta可撑不到一周
Loretta doesn't have all week
其他感染者也撑不了这么久
and neither do the other victims.
我们得另找办法来查出做这事的人 得快
We need another way to find out who did this, fast.
我这儿可能有所发现
Might have something in here.
我一直在查谋杀发生时
Been I.D.-ing every person and car
每个进了Angelo Brocato's的人
in or around Angelo Brocato's
以及在附近逗留的人和车
around the time of the baker's murder.
什么都没看到 直到...
Nothing came up until...
我们发现一辆驶过的银色丰田四驱车的车牌
We matched the license plate to a silver Toyota 4Runner
和两天前上报失窃的车牌匹配上了
reported stolen two days ago driving by.
晚上9:33
9:33 p.m.
可能是个巧合 或者
Could be a coincidence, or...
可能是我们要找的特工 干得好
Could be our operatives. Good work.
我会发布一个协查通告 同时通知州警和FBI
I'll put a BOLO out, notify LSP and FBI, too.
我们要不要触发紧急报警系统 扩大影响
Should we trigger EAS, go wide?
-我是说 这实在... -不 不 不
- I mean, it's just... - No, no, no, no, no.
媒体一旦抓住这个事 放出风去
The media gets ahold of this and puts it out there,
可能会引起恐慌
could cause a panic that the virus
以为病毒已经扩散到基地外
is gonna spread beyond the base.
这只会让我们更难找到那些特工
Make it all that more difficult to find our operatives.
卫生部门已经知道了
Well, the health department already knows.
他们对Wade的停尸房进行了病毒隔离
They quarantined Wade's morgue.
媒体发现这件事只是时间问题
It's just a matter of time before the media finds out.
对 随后就会引起公众恐慌
Yep, and stokes public fear.
我们必须控制住局势
We have to keep this contained.
只有一种办法能控制了
Only one way to do that.
你们找到车就立即告诉我
Let me know when you find that car.
他要去哪儿
Where's he going?
我敢说是他最不想去的地方
I bet it's the last place he wants to go.
你碰上硬茬了 Dwayne 我就跟你说这些
You got stones, Dwayne, I'll give you that much.
我俩都不希望媒体抓住这个新闻
Last thing we both need is for the media to get ahold of this.
他们已经和我办公室联系过了 还不止一次
They've already contacted my office, more than once.
媒体的歇斯底里对我找出幕后黑手毫无帮助
Media hysteria is not gonna help me find out who's responsible.
事实上 反而会增加难度
In fact, it'll hurt the cause.
我有线索了 只需要一两天 或许更快
I got a lead, just need a day or two, maybe less.
可是 我不是很擅长对民众撒谎
Still, I couldn't very well lie to the people.
如果我很善于撒谎 就不会成为好市长了 对吧
I wouldn't be a very good mayor if I did, now would I?
很明显 公共卫生办公室也打电话了
Apparently the Office of Public Health is getting calls, too.
他们在寻求一份官方声明
They're asking for an official statement.
顺便问一句 Loretta如何了
And by the way, how's Loretta doing?
真够丢脸的 对吧
Real shame, isn't it?
你几个意思
So, what?
你是在针对我吗
You're gonna make this personal, is that it?
这事关阻止一场病毒爆发
This is about trying to stop an outbreak,
拯救无辜人员 这不是我们的私人恩怨 Hamilton
saving innocent people; this isn't about us, Hamilton.
去你的不是私人恩怨
The hell it's not about us.
Garcia事件后 我们的每件事都是私人恩怨
Everything's about us since Garcia.
你也许不这么看 Dwayne 但事实是
You may not see this, Dwayne, but the truth is
我们的目的是相同的 都是为了这个城市好
we both want the same thing: what's good for this city.
唯一的问题在于
The only problem is that you think
你认为扳倒我是达到目的的最好方法
that bringing me down is the best way to do that,
而我不能让这事发生
and I can't allow that to happen.
你想怎样
So what do you want?
我想要你手头所有关于我的证据
I want whatever you got on me.
所有你认为的关于我的证据
Whatever you think you got.
当面 Garcia案的证据
Vis-à-vis Garcia.
听起来像是向我认罪了
Sounds like an admission to me.
我没承认任何事
Not admitting anything.
我只想让你离我远远的
I just want you off my back once and for all.
所以你为了掩饰自己的罪行
So you're threatening to impede my investigation,
不惜冒着扩散恐慌的危险来威胁我 妨碍我调查
risk causing widespread fear just to cover your own ass?
你才是一直在威胁别人的人
You're the one doing the threatening,
而我不打算继续容忍下去了
and I'm not gonna stand for it,
哪怕这意味着要把你
not anymore, even if it means getting you
和你的整个见鬼的团队踢出新奥尔良
and your whole damn team kicked out of New Orleans.
NCIS是联邦机构
NCIS is federal.
你没有权力和管辖权...
You don't have the power or the jurisdiction...
哦 伙计 只要你有人脉
Oh, man, jurisdiction doesn't mean anything
管辖权没有任何意义
if you got connections.
我跟国防部长是老交情了
And me and SECDEF go way back,
相信我
believe me.
很明显 有一种东西叫做
Apparently, there's something called
流动协议
a mobility agreement.
协议上说 如果海军高官认为
Says that if Navy brass thinks
NCIS和这座城市相处得不是很好
NCIS and the city aren't getting along,
他们能把你们重新派到天知道什么地方去
well, they can re-assign you to God knows where.
游戏结束了 Dwayne
Gloves are off, Dwayne.
你想要我帮忙吗
You want my help, hmm?
想要我合作 除非
Cooperation? That only happens
明天这个时间 你把你搞到的关于Garcia的一切都给我
you get me everything you got on Garcia by this time tomorrow.
明白了吗
Understand?
我们的协查通告没有回应
We didn't get a BOLO hit,
但是Patton一直在追踪这一片的
but Patton's been tracking satellite radio signals
所有四驱车的卫星无线信号
from every 4Runner in the area,
发现有一个突然消失了
when one suddenly vanished.
-我想我们发现它了 -Gregorio
- I think we just found it. - Gregorio.
-看这里 -是什么
- Look at this. - What is it?
我很确定这是Lopez
I'm pretty sure it's Lopez.
Lopez在里面 Pride
Lopez is inside, Pride.
她死了
She's dead.
一定有人发现她在调查了
Must've caught her investigating.
后座上还有两个人
Two more in the backseat.
等等 还有两个
Wait. Two more?
他们是谁
Who are they?
我刚通过受害者的DNA确定了他们的身份
I just got DNA I.D.s on both victims,
但我觉得你们不会喜欢的
but I'm afraid you're not gonna like this.
他们是陆战队员
They're marines.
我把档案发给你们
I'm sending the files to you now.
Loretta 你必须休息了
Loretta, you have to lie down.
我们讨论过这个问题了 Dwayne
We've been through this, Dwayne.
我们都知道我不是唯一一个时日无多的人
We both know I'm not the only one running out of time.
等等 他们不只是一般的陆战队员
Wait a second, those aren't just any marines.
好吗 他们是赶往Belle Chasse的
All right? They're part of a Biological Response Force
生化响应部队的队员
that was headed for Belle Chasse.
等等 特工们杀了Lopez
Wait, operatives killed Lopez
是因为她在调查他们 这我能理解
because she was investigating them-- that much I get.
但是为什么截杀了另外两个人
But why intercept and kill the other two?
是不想让他们阻止病毒爆发吗
Try to keep them from stopping the outbreak?
等等 根据Belle Chasse的出入记录
Hold on. According to the Belle Chasse
Davis下士和Lin下士
entry log, Corporals Davis and Lin
刚刚跟他们的部队一起进了大门
just checked in at the main gate along with their unit.
所以特工们一定潜伏在里面
So operatives must have snuck in,
在他们跟陆战护卫队一起出行的时候
killed them while they were traveling
杀掉了他们
with the marine convoy.
但是他们做这一切只是为了偷取他们的身份牌吗
But they did all that just to steal their I.D.s?
这说不通啊
Well, that doesn't make any sense.
我是说 基地里有人被感染
I mean, if they're with the people that infected the base,
那一定是他们最不想去的地方
that'd be the last place they'd want to go.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
Sebastian正在Belle Chasse
Sebastian's at Belle Chasse
等候响应部队
waiting for the Response Force.
也就是说 他完全不知道这两个人的真实身份
Which means he has no idea who those people really are.
你们是响应部队的吗
You guys from the Response Force?
是 准下士Lin和Davis
Yeah. Lance Corporal Lin, Davis.
其他人在路上
Rest of the team's on its way.
-你是谁 -海军罪案调查处 法医探员Lund.
- Who are you? - NCIS, Forensic Agent Lund.
我来这里调查事件发生的原因
I'm here to figure out how this all happened,
但更重要的是 阻止事件进一步恶化
but more importantly, how we can stop it.
跟我来 穿好装备
Come on, let's get geared up.
直接转到了语音信箱
Straight to voice mail.
我们必须去趟基地
We got to get to the base.
Christopher 继续打
Christopher, keep calling
Sebastian的电话
Sebastian on his cell.
我会通知海军情报局
I'll call ONI.
Gregorio
Gregorio,
通知基地的警察
get the base police
守住Belle Chasse基地
to secure Belle Chasses,
严密控制各个大门
put the gates on high alert.
Loretta 一有消息马上告诉你 我保证
Loretta, I'll call you as soon as we know anything, promise.
嘿 Wade医生
Hey! Dr. Wade!
最近一次使用的抗生素也没有效果
Last antibiotic isn't working, either.
给我碳青霉烯 亚治疗抗生素疗法
Get me carbapenem, stat.
sub-therapeutic antibiotic treatment
准备插管治疗
Let's intubate her.
来 来 快点 伙计
Come on, come on. Hurry up, people.
如果想救她 就得先让她稳定下来
If we want to save her, we've got to stabilize her.
她还有意识吗 能说话吗
Is she conscious, talking?
好 你告诉她保重
All right, you tell her to take care
我们这边会竭尽全力
and that we're out here doing everything we can on our end.
-谢谢 -Wade怎么样了
- Thank you. - How's Wade?
医生打算让她进入药物性昏迷状态
Thinking about putting her in a medically induced coma
延缓新陈代谢 争取更多时间
to slow her metabolism, buy time.
她还剩多长时间
How much time she have?
-不多了 -Pride探员
- Not much. - Agent Pride.
我是Rogers上校 基地指挥官
I'm Captain Rogers, Base Commanding Officer here.
找到我的探员了吗
Any luck finding my agent?
还没有 这个基地很大 我们还在搜索
Not yet, but it's a large base; we're still searching.
但基地已经全面戒严 每个出口都被控制
But we're under full lockdown, every access point guarded.
特工不可能从我们眼皮底下
Operatives won't be able to escape
-逃跑 -好的 但要注意
- without going through us. - Okay, well, the problem is
我们必须活捉他们
we got to take them alive.
只有他们可能有解毒剂
They may be the only ones with an antidote.
还是没找到Sebastian King
Still can't reach Sebastian, King.
他为什么要关机呢
Why would he turn off his phone?
他不会的
He wouldn't.
基地有什么区域会屏蔽手机信号吗
Is there a secure area on base where cell phones are jammed?
有 确实有
Yes, there is.
Downey中校 海军情报局
Commander Downey, Naval Intelligence.
-我们之前通过话 跟我来 -是 长官
- We spoke earlier. Follow me. -Yes, sir.
看来我们最终还是获得了权限
Looks like we finally got clearance.
希望如此 迟到总比不到好
Hopefully. Better late than never.
我会在路上告诉你们情况 我有车
I'll download you on the way. I got a vehicle.
我还是不明白 我们来这儿做什么
I still don't know why we're here
我们为什么要穿防护服
or why we're wearing protective gear.
Campbell士官的血液微粒无处不在
P.O. Campbell's blood particulates could be anywhere.
对 可是这地方已经清理干净了
Yeah, but the area's already been cleared.
我们要做的是测试感染者
What we need to be doing is testing the infected
获取有抵抗性的抗体
for resistant antibodies.
这是我们的管辖范围 Lund探员
This is our jurisdiction, Agent Lund,
不是你的
not yours.
-有问题吗 -没 没问题了
- There a problem? - No. Everything's good.
好 检查外面的残留污染物
All right. Check for residual contamination
我们负责检查里面
out here, we'll check inside.
走
Let's go.
麻烦了
Crap.
我们认为 这次生物袭击只是为了转移我们的注意力
We think the biological attack was really just a diversion
好让间谍混进基地
to get the operatives on base.
谋杀海军响应部队 盗用他们的身份
By killing the Marine Response Force.
因为他们知道 响应部队会是第一个来支援的
Because they knew they'd be the first ones called in,
海军的报警方式
Navy 911.
正是
Exactly.
但他们有什么目的 为什么要这么做
But to do what? Why go through all this?
-障眼法么 -可能是
- Smokescreen? - Probably.
潜入绝密区域的最好办法就是
Best way to breach a highly-secure area:
制造大范围恐慌
create widespread panic.
Lopez少校的团队
Commander Lopez's team
安装安全电缆通向船只激活中心
was installing secure cables to what D.O.D. had hoped
国防部希望该中心成为圣地亚哥东部
would become the first ship activation center
-第一个船只激活中心 -船只激活中心
- east of San Diego. - Ship activation?
你得了解军舰的工作原理
You have to understand how Navy ships work.
它们在被编入海军序列前
They're basically just floating hunks of metal
本质上只是漂浮的金属而已
until they're programmed into warships.
这个流程是绝密的
It's a highly classified procedure,
希望是利用这个基地来扩大我们的覆盖面
and the hope was this base could expand our reach.
激活的船只越多
The more ships activated,
中国越难以应对
the more the Chinese have to contend with.
他们不希望这种事发生
They don't want that to happen.
很显然 他们会不惜任何代价
At all costs, apparently.
他们究竟要做什么
So what do they want?
想怎样阻止这项计划
How do they expect to stop the programming?
偷走激活船只的中央处理器
Steal the ship activation CPU
以及全部储存着的情报
and all the stored Intel.
使国防部对Belle Chasse基地失去信任
Make D.O.D. lose faith in Belle Chasse.
Sebastian
Sebastian.
趴下 趴下
Get down, get down!
好了 去看看Sebastian
All right, check on Sebastian.
警戒大门 我们必须活捉他们
Alert the gate. We need them taken alive.
-快走 -嫌疑人朝正门开去
- Let's go! - Suspects headed to main gate.
逮捕 留活口 重复 逮捕 留活口
Capture, do not kill. Repeat, capture, do not kill.
行动
Now.
铺开钉刺带 快 快 快
Deploy the spike strip! Go, go, go!
-停火 -停火
- Hold your fire! - Cease fire!
停止射击 你们逃不了 你们已经被包围了
Stop shooting! There's nowhere to go; you're surrounded!
手伸出窗户 马上
Hands out the window, now.
现在就伸出来
Do it now!
伸出窗外 慢慢地
Outside the window, slow!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
明白 但还是拜托了 尽你所能
Understood. Please, though, just do everything you can.
在我看到这些嫌疑犯时 就应该看穿他们
I should have known the moment I saw that those operatives
他们的腕部没有密封 不知道怎么的我就忽略了
didn't tape up their wrists-- I don't know how I missed it.
Sebastian 你已经尽力了 你跟踪他们
Sebastian, you did your best. You-you followed them,
你与他们交火 火力压制住了他们
you engaged them. You-you were outgunned.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I mean.
我是说 我知道他们是犯罪分子 我居然没想到
I mean, I knew that they were bad guys, it just didn't
他们之所以不用害怕被感染
occur to me that the only reason they weren't afraid
是因为他们已经接种过了
of being infected was 'cause they had been inoculated.
解毒剂就在他们身体里
The antidote was already in their system.
我应该早点意识到那点
I should've figured that out sooner.
也不会有任何改变的
Wouldn't have made any difference.
他们不会被活捉的
They weren't gonna be taken alive.
他们受训保护国家机密
They're trained to protect state secrets.
知道么 不计代价
All right? No matter the cost.
Sebastian 你可以复制抗体吗
Sebastian, hey, can you duplicate it?
我现在正试着分离抗体
I'm-I'm trying to separate the antibodies right now,
但是Wade没有那么多的时间
but Wade doesn't have that much time.
King Patton在激活中央处理器的事情上
Hey, King, Patton may have found something
有了发现
off the activation CPU...
我现在不关心这个案子 Christopher
I don't care about the case right now, Christopher.
这与案子无关 与Wade有关
It's not about the case, it's about Wade.
我们发现中央处理器连接到了
We found the CPU hooked up to the docking station
特工货车里的扩展基站
in the operative's van.
我们在追捕他们的时候 他们正在上传资料
They were uploading it to someone while we were
-给别人 -对 不在现场的某个人
- chasing them. - Yeah, someone off-site.
他们知道自己不能活着离开
They must've knew they weren't getting out of there alive.
但是还想转移情报
But they still wanted to transfer the Intel
给他们的上司
to whoever they were working for,
或许就是负责人
probably the handler.
你能追踪到信号么
Can you trace the signal?
这就是我们找你的原因
That's why we're calling.
正在追查接收者的IP地址
Tracking down the receiver's I.P. address,
确定方位 准备行动
vectoring the location. Stand by.
Pride 如果我们能找到负责人
Pride, if we can find the handler...
为了预防被感染
There's a good chance he might have
他很可能有解毒剂
the antidote on him as a precaution.
找到了 正在发送
Got it, sending it now.
在Chalmette的Alferd Supply
Alferd Supply in Chalmette.
在那儿会合
We'll meet you there.
NCIS 举起手来
NCIS! Get your hands up!
联邦探员 不准动
Federal agents! Don't move!
嘿
Hey!
氰化物
Cyanide.
-安全 -好的 开始搜索
- Clear. - Okay. Start searching everywhere.
解药一定在这儿的某个地方
That antidote's got to be here somewhere.
我们肯定不是在浪费时间
So we're not wasting time here.
你因涉嫌谋杀
You are under arrest for murder,
恐怖袭击与间谍活动被捕
terrorism, espionage.
但这些我一点儿也不关心
But I don't care about any of that.
我只想要病毒的解药
All I want is to get the antidote to the virus.
病毒 什么病毒
Virus? What virus?
你现在别想来烦我
You do not want to mess with me right now,
知道了吗
do you understand that?
因为你 我的朋友就要死了
My friend is dying because of you,
如果你不帮我救她
and if you don't help me save her...
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die.
不怕吗
No?
如果死得很快 可能你不怕 但
Not quickly, maybe, but...
慢慢地死呢
how about slowly?
痛苦地死 就像那些受害者
Painfully, like all your victims.
把病毒直接注射到
You know, uh, injecting the baker
蛋糕师体内
directly with the virus...
那一定会让他死得更加痛苦
...that must've made his death that much more excruciating.
他的大脑迅速膨胀
His brain probably swelled up immediately,
肺里充满血 溺死的感觉
lungs filled with blood, drowning him,
抽搐
convulsions.
你不能这样做
You can't do this.
他不能 但我能
He can't, but I can.
这里没人能阻止我
And there's nobody's here to stop me.
不 等等 那张桌子
No, wait! The table!
解毒剂在那张牌桌下
The antidote's under the card table!
找到了
Got it.
好 送到基地和Loretta那儿 快点
All right, get it to the base and Loretta. Hurry!
Sebastian
Sebastian.
你真的会给他注射吗
Were you really gonna inject him?
为了她 我会的
For her, yeah.
去吧
Get going.
现在怎么办
What now?
现在我们要指控你
Now we're gonna book you.
我们有许多
We got a treasure trove
指控你的证据
of incriminating evidence against you.
逃过死刑的唯一方法可能
Probably the only way to get out of the death penalty
就是交代出你的上头
is if you admit to who you're working for.
我不会告诉你的
You're not getting that out of me.
我认为你要担心的不是我们
Well, I don't think it's us you got to worry about.
你要担心国安局和国土安全部反恐部门
Oh, no, that's NSA and DHS territory,
如果我没记错的话 关塔那摩监狱...
but if my memory serves me, Guantanamo...
怎么回事
What the hell?
有人竟然通过砖墙开枪杀了他
Someone just shot him through a friggin' brick wall!
好
Okay.
弹壳
Bullet casing.
还是热的
Still warm.
零点五口径的吗
Is that .50 caliber?
不是一般的零点五口径子弹
Not just any .50 caliber.
能穿过砖墙
Penetrates through a brick wall
看不见目标 还能击中目标
without line of sight and still hits its target?
一定是国防部高级研究计划局的产品 热感器 热量搜寻器
It's got to be DARPA, thermal scope, heat seeking.
一定还有别人
Must have been another operative
想要确保他闭嘴
who wanted to make sure that this one didn't talk.
但我不认为那人是中国人
Except I don't think the operative was Chinese.
这是美国的技术 Pride
This is U.S. technology, Pride.
也是尖端技术
It's brand-new, too.
不管是谁干的 一定是个土生土长的美国人
Which means whoever did this had to be homegrown American.
敲敲门
Knock, knock.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey! - Hey.
感觉怎么样了
How you feeling?
这问题有点蠢
That's sort of a stupid question, I know.
对不起 我不知道在这样的情况下
I'm sorry. It's-- I-I don't know how to act
该做什么 我是说 显然
in situations like this. I mean, obviously,
在你经历了这些事以后
after everything you've been through,
你感觉并不好 但同时
you're not feeling great, but at the same time,
-我也不知道我 - Sebastian
- I don't know what I'm... - Sebastian.
再问我一遍
Just ask me again.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
我感觉很糟
I feel like crap.
但我活下来了 所以我也能接受 谢谢你
But I'm alive and I'll take it, thanks to you.
谢我吗 不 我不能
Thanks to me? No, I can't...
别那么说
Oh, don't even go there.
Pride已经告诉我了
Pride already told me what you did.
说你救了我的命
Said you saved my life.
我是说
I mean...
我没有
I didn't, you know.
算不上有 不是我一个人救的
Not really. Not by myself.
-算是团队合作 -过来
- It was sort of, like, a group... - Come here.
想给你个拥抱
Want to give you a hug.
嗯
Mm.
谢谢你
Thank you.
随时
Anytime.
我为你骄傲 Sebastian
I'm proud of you, Sebastian.
你直面恐惧
You faced your fears.
你冒着生命危险拯救别人
You risked your life to save others.
我听说你甚至威胁了那混蛋
I heard you even threatened to go a little rogue.
那就是我听到的事
That's what I heard.
是啊
Yeah, well, you know.
这意味着 我终于成了一名真正的探员了
Guess that means I'm finally becoming a real agent.
不
No.
这意味着 你终于成为了你自己
Means you're finally becoming yourself.
嘿
Hey.
打扰到你了吗
Am I interrupting?
没有
No.
-没 有什么事 -我想应该告诉你
- No. What's up? - Just thought you'd like to know
我问了Belle Chasse的医生
I checked with the medic at Belle Chasse.
所有人都在康复
Everyone's recovering.
很好 很好
Good. Good.
前几天真是大起大落啊 对吧
Kind of a major whirlwind last couple of days, huh?
还不敢相信发生了这些事情
I still can't believe everything that happened.
还有那些差点发生的事
And everything that almost happened.
是啊 但很奇怪啊
Right? So strange, though.
所有事都会沉寂
All that goes down all the time,
人们不会知道发生什么
public never even knows about it.
有时不那么容易保密
Not easy keeping it that way sometimes.
还有别的事吗
Something else?
有
Yeah.
我在杀死那个负责人的
I, uh, got a partial fingerprint
零点五口径的弹壳上 发现了部分指纹
on the .50 caliber cartridge that killed our handler.
-找出身份信息了吗 - 没有
- You get an I.D.? - No.
但我想你会觉得这很有趣
But I think you'll find this interesting.
这指纹结果与
Turns out the print matches the partial
Sebastian在Garcia引爆装置上提取到的指纹相同
Sebastian lifted off of Garcia's detonator you guys found.
是的
Yep.
同一个人杀了他们两个
Same person killed both people.
等等
But wait.
如果是真的 那就意味着
If that's true, then that would mean...
那意味着
That would mean
杀手为Hamilton市长工作
the killer's working for Mayor Hamilton,
也意味着
which also means
Hamilton可能是这两起凶杀案的幕后黑手
Hamilton could be behind both killings.
如果是这样的话
And, if so,
不管市长担当了什么角色
whatever the good mayor is up to
都要比我们想象得权力大
is a lot bigger than we thought.
难怪他要威胁我们
No wonder he's trying to threaten us.
你来晚了 Dwayne
You're late, Dwayne.
我以为你不会来
Thought you weren't gonna show.
不想让你失望 市长先生
Wouldn't want to disappoint you, Mr. Mayor.
很好 我很高兴
Good, I'm glad.
那是给我的吗
That for me?
是的
Yeah.
等等 等等 这是什么
Whoa, wait, wait. Wh-What is this?
我告诉过你 我要你手中关于Garcia被杀一案的所有资料
I told you I wanted everything you had on Garcia's murder.
我记得
I remember.
放马过来
Gloves are off.
你说的
Your words.